tabscout.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - TabScout

    **Your Privacy**

    TabScout.com is committed to protecting your privacy.
    TabScout.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies.
    TabScout.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically
    and knowingly provide such information.

    By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TabScout.com.
    At some point TabScout may share information with selected partners who work with us to deliver services.
    If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are
    always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
    Currently, TabScout.com may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related 
    site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal
    identifying information.

    Newsletter Anti-Spam Policy tolerates only permission-based email. In addition, users always have the opportunity
    to opt-out or change preferences via a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages.
    These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from our company.
    Alternatively, you may email us. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited commercial email from Newsletter
    on behalf of any of our customers, you may report it to us.
    
    **Modification of Privacy Policy**

    TabScout.com reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you
    agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
